Finding Aid for the J. Warren Perry Collection of Photographs, circa 1910-1971
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- People, circa 1910-1971, I.; 1199 photographs
  - Mildred Miller as Octavian, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 10, Item C10-026)
  - Nathan Milstein, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 10, Item C10-027)
  - Mischa Mischakoff, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 10, Item C10-028)
  - Dimitri Mitropoulos, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 10, Item C10-029)
  - Dimitri Mitropoulos, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Balon (Box 10, Item C10-030)
  - Dimitri Mitropoulos, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Balon (Box 10, Item C10-031)
  - Dimitri Mitropoulos, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 10, Item C10-032)
  - Dimitri Mitropoulos, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 10, Item C10-033)
  - Dimitri Mitropoulos, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 10, Item C10-034)
  - Dimitri Mitropoulos in rehearsal, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Levi (Florence, Italy) (Box 10, Item C10-035)
  - Martha Mödl as Kundry, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 10, Item C10-036)
  - Martha Mödl as Brunnhilde, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 10, Item C10-037)
  - Martha Mödl as Brunnhilde, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 10, Item C10-038)
  - Anna Moffo as Nannetta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 10, Item C10-039)
  - Anna Moffo as Nannetta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 10, Item C10-040)
  - Anna Moffo as Lucia, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Studio Boieri (Box 10, Item C10-041)
  - Anna Moffo as Violetta, 1959?, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 10, Item C10-042)
  - Anna Moffo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 10, Item C10-043)
  - Anna Moffo as Violetta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 10, Item C10-044)
  - Anna Moffo with William Wildermann, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 10, Item C10-045)
  - Benno Moiseiwitsch, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Underwood & Underwood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 10, Item C10-046)
  - Pierre Monteux, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Flamm, Roy (Box 10, Item C10-047)
  - Pierre Monteux, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Flamm, Roy (Box 10, Item C10-048)
  - Pierre Monteux, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 10, Item C10-049)
  - Pierre Monteux, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 10, Item C10-050)
  - Pierre Monteux, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 10, Item C10-051)
  - Nicola Monti as Elvino, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 10, Item C10-052)
  - Jean Morel, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Halsman (New York, N.Y.) (Box 10, Item C10-053)
  - Erica Morini, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C10-054)
  - Elsie Morison as Susanna in The Marriage of Figaro, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 10, Item C10-055)
  - Barry Morell as Rodolfo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 10, Item C10-056)
  - Barry Morell as Alfredo Germont, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 10, Item C10-057)
  - Nicola Moscona, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 10, Item C10-058)
  - Nicola Moscona as Ramfis, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 10, Item C10-059)
  - Nicola Moscona as the Grand Inquisitor in Don Carlos, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 10, Item C10-060)
  - Charles Munch, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Jac-Guy (Montreal, Quebec) (Box 10, Item C10-061)
  - Charles Munch, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bachrach, Fabian, 1917- (Box 10, Item C10-062)
  - Claudia Muzio as Loreley, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Rosenofeld (?), M (Box 10, Item C10-063)
  - Claudia Muzio as Leonora in Il Trovatore, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Van Riel, B.A (Box 10, Item C10-064)
  - Patrice Munsel as Adele, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 10, Item C10-065)
  - Patrice Munsel as Gilda, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 10, Item C10-066)
  - Patrice Munsel as Lucia, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 10, Item C10-067)
  - Ms. note from Patricia Munsel, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 10, Item C10-068)
  - Patrice Munsel as Perichole, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 10, Item C10-069)
  - Patrice Munsel, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 10, Item C10-070)
  - Elly Ney, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-001)
  - Elena Nicola in La Fiamma, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 11, Item C11-002)
  - Elena Nicola in Norma, 1955-1956, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 11, Item C11-003)
  - Elena Nicola in Elektra, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 11, Item C11-004)
  - Birgit Nilsson as Turandot, 1958-1959, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 11, Item C11-005)
  - Birgit Nilsson as Isolde, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 11, Item C11-006)
  - Birgit Nilsson as Senta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-007)
  - Birgit Nilsson as Brunnhilde, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-008)
  - Birgit Nilsson as Turandot, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-009)
  - Birgit Nilsson as Brunnhilde, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-010)
  - Birgit Nilsson, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 11, Item C11-011)
  - Birgit Nilsson as Isolde with Karl Liebl as Tristan, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 11, Item C11-012)
  - Birgit Nilsson as Brunnhilde, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 11, Item C11-013)
  - Birgit Nilsson as Turandot, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-014)
  - Birgit Nilsson as Brunnhilde with Jerome Hines as Wotan, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 11, Item C11-015)
  - Elena Nikolaidi as Amneris, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 11, Item C11-016)
  - Elena Nikolaidi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 11, Item C11-017)
  - Typescript note from Elena Nikolaidi, 1953 May 21, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-018)
  - Guiomar Novaes, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Le Boux, Yvonne (Box 11, Item C11-019)
  - Guiomar Novaes, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Le Boux, Yvonne (Box 11, Item C11-020)
  - Jarmila Novotna as Violetta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-021)
  - Jarmila Novotna as Octavian, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-022)
  - David Oistrakh, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Allen, Derek (Box 11, Item C11-023)
  - David Oistrakh, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-024)
  - Magda Olivero as Fedora Romanov, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-025)
  - Magda Olivero as Margherita, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 11, Item C11-026)
  - Magda Olivero as Liu, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 11, Item C11-027)
  - William Olvis as Malcolm, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 11, Item C11-028)
  - Sigrid Onegin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Stiffel (Munich, Germany) (Box 11, Item C11-029)
  - Eugene Ormandy, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-030)
  - Eugene Ormandy, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Halsman (New York, N.Y.) (Box 11, Item C11-031)
  - Eugene Ormandy, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Halsman (New York, N.Y.) (Box 11, Item C11-032)
  - Eugene Ormandy, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Meitner-Graf, Lotte, (London, England) (Box 11, Item C11-033)
  - Eugene Ormandy, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-034)
  - Eugene Ormandy, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-035)
  - Eugene Ormandy, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fehl, Fred (Box 11, Item C11-036)
  - Eugene Ormandy, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-037)
  - Eugene Ormandy, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-038)
  - Eugene Ormandy, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Halsman (New York, N.Y.) (Box 11, Item C11-039)
  - Eugene Ormandy, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-040)
  - Eugene Ormandy, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-041)
  - Mario Ortica as Radames, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-042)
  - Ignacy Paderewski, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-043)
  - Hands of Ignacy Paderewski, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-044)
  - Rolando Panerai as Mathis, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 11, Item C11-045)
  - Rolando Panerai in Musorgsky's The Fair at Sorochintsi, 1954-1955, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 11, Item C11-046)
  - Rolando Panerai in Prokofiev's The Fiery Angel, 1956-1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 11, Item C11-047)
  - Conductor Paul Paray rehearsing the Detroit Symphony Orchestra, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-048)
  - Program biography of Paul Paray, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-049)
  - Paul Paray, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Clinedinst (Box 11, Item C11-050)
  - Drawing of Paul Paray, 1953, 1 black and white photograph; Hall, R. (artist) (Box 11, Item C11-051)
  - Paul Paray, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lipnitzki (Paris, France) (Box 11, Item C11-052)
  - Paul Paray, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-053)
  - Paul Paray, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-054)
  - Paul Paray, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-055)
  - Adelina Patti, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Gebbie & Husson (Box 11, Item C11-056)
  - Gerhard Pechner as Sacristan in Tosca, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-057)
  - Gerhard Pechner as the Sheriff in Martha, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 11, Item C11-058)
  - Jan Peerce as Edgardo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-059)
  - Jan Peerce as Alfredo Germont, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-060)
  - Jan Peerce as the Duke of Mantua, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-061)
  - Jan Peerce as Riccardo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-062)
  - Wilfrid Pelletier, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 11, Item C11-063)
  - Gino Penno as Radames, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 11, Item C11-064)
  - Gino Penno as Radames, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 11, Item C11-065)
  - Gino Penno Manrico, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 11, Item C11-066)
  - Roberta Peters as Rosina, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 11, Item C11-067)
  - Roberta Peters as Gilda, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 11, Item C11-068)
  - Roberta Peters, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-069)
  - Roberta Peters as Gilda, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 11, Item C11-070)
  - Roberta Peters as Adele, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 11, Item C11-071)
  - Roberta Peters as Queen of the Night, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 11, Item C11-072)
  - Roberta Peters as Rosina with Cesare Valletti as Count Almaviva, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 11, Item C11-073)
  - Roberta Peters with husband Bertram Fields, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 11, Item C11-074)
  - Clara Petrella as Adriana, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 11, Item C11-075)
  - Clara Petrella in Pizzetti's La figlia di Iorio, 1955-1956, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 11, Item C11-076)
  - Egon Petri, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Gilpin, Laura (Box 11, Item C11-077)
  - Gregor Piatigorsky, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Orkin, Ruth (Box 12, Item C12-001)
  - Gregor Piatigorsky, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-002)
  - Drawing of Gregor Piatigorsky, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Adams, Wayman, 1883-1959 (Box 12, Item C12-003)
  - Mirto Picchi as Pollione, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-004)
  - Mirto Picchi as Tom Rakewell, 1951-1952, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 12, Item C12-005)
  - Ezio Pinza as Don Giovanni, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-006)
  - Ezio Pinza as Don Giovanni, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-007)
  - Walter Piston, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-008)
  - Marcella Pobbe as Marguerite, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 12, Item C12-009)
  - Gianni Poggi as Cavaradossi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 12, Item C12-010)
  - Gianni Poggi as Fernand, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Bisazza, E (Box 12, Item C12-011)
  - David Poleri as Don Alvaro, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-012)
  - Lily Pons as Lakme, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-013)
  - Lily Pons as Marie in Fille du regiment, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-014)
  - Lily Pons as Violetta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-015)
  - Lily Pons as Lucia, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bender (Box 12, Item C12-016)
  - Lily Pons, undated, 1 black and white photograph; De Bellis (New York, N.Y.) (Box 12, Item C12-017)
  - Lily Pons, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-018)
  - Lily Pons as Gilda, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-019)
  - Rosa Ponselle as Carmen, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-020)
  - Rosa Ponselle, Jose Mardones, and Enrico Caruso in La Forza del destino, 1918 Nov. 15 ?, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-021)
  - Giacinto Prandelli as Alfredo Germont, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 12, Item C12-022)
  - Giacinto Prandelli as Werther, 1950-1951, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 12, Item C12-023)
  - Milton Preves, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-024)
  - Fernando Previtali, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-025)
  - Fernando Previtali, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Waga (Box 12, Item C12-026)
  - Leontyne Price as Thais, 1959, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 12, Item C12-027)
  - Leontyne Price as Thais, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 12, Item C12-028)
  - Leontyne Price, Dorothy Kirsten, and Sylvia Stahlman in The Carmelites, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 12, Item C12-029)
  - William Primrose, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mitchell, Herbert, (New York, N.Y.) (Box 12, Item C12-030)
  - William Primrose, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Jackson, Ray Lee (Box 12, Item C12-031)
  - Sergey Prokofiev, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-032)
  - Sergey Prokofiev, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-033)
  - Sergey Prokofiev with conductor Nicolai Malko, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-034)
  - Aldo Protti as Rigoletto, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 12, Item C12-035)
  - Aldo Protti in La Forza del destino, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 12, Item C12-036)
  - Florence Quartararo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-037)
  - Michael Rabin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 12, Item C12-038)
  - Sergei Rachmaninoff, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-039)
  - Gianni Raimondi as Pinkerton, 1957-1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 12, Item C12-040)
  - Gianni Raimondi as Alfredo Germont, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 12, Item C12-041)
  - Gianni Raimondi as Wilhelm Meister, 1957-1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 12, Item C12-042)
  - Rosa Raisa, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-043)
  - Rosa Raisa, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-044)
  - Rosa Raisa with Carol Fox, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Quality Photographers (Box 12, Item C12-045)
  - Herva Nelli as Aida, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 12, Item C12-046)
  - Nell Rankin as Amneris, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 12, Item C12-047)
  - Nell Rankin as Marina, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 12, Item C12-048)
  - Nell Rankin as Amneris, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 12, Item C12-049)
  - Fritz Reiner, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bender (Box 12, Item C12-050)
  - Fritz Reiner, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bender (Box 12, Item C12-051)
  - Nicola Rescigno, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Halsman (New York, N.Y.) (Box 12, Item C12-052)
  - Nicola Rescigno, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 12, Item C12-053)
  - Regina Resnik as Carmen, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-054)
  - Regina Resnik as the Baroness in Vanessa, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 12, Item C12-055)
  - Ottorino Respighi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-056)
  - Elisabeth Rethberg, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mishkin Studio (New York, N.Y.) ? (Box 12, Item C12-057)
  - Typescript letter from Frederick C. Kraus on behalf of Elizabeth Rethberg, 1950, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 12, Item C12-058)
  - Ruggiero Ricci, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-001)
  - Delia Rigal as Elisabeth di Valois, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 13, Item C13-002)
  - Delia Rigal as Violetta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-003)
  - Rudolf Ringwall, Assoc. conductor of Cleveland Orch., undated, 1 black and white photograph; Strauss, Ben (Box 13, Item C13-004)
  - Margherita Roberti as Desdemona, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-005)
  - Margherita Roberti with Boris Christoff, Tito Gobbi, Richard Tucker, Giulietta Simionato, Franco Ventriglia, and Antonio Votto, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-006)
  - Margaret Roggero as Berta, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 13, Item C13-007)
  - Stella Roman, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-008)
  - Stella Roman, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-009)
  - Leonard Rose, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 13, Item C13-010)
  - Leonard Rose, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 13, Item C13-011)
  - Nicola Rossi Lemeni as Archibaldo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 13, Item C13-012)
  - Nicola Rossi Lemeni as Boris Godunov, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Dinami (Buenos Aires, Argentina) (Box 13, Item C13-013)
  - Nicola Rossi Lemeni as Boris Godunov, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Dinami (Buenos Aires, Argentina) (Box 13, Item C13-014)
  - Nicola Rossi Lemeni as Don Giovanni, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-015)
  - Nicola Rossi Lemeni as Mephistopheles, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 13, Item C13-016)
  - Nicola Rossi Lemeni as King Philippe II, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 13, Item C13-017)
  - Nicola Rossi Lemeni as Boris Godunov, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 13, Item C13-018)
  - Nicola Rossi Lemeni as Boris Godunov, 1955-1956, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 13, Item C13-019)
  - Nicola Rossi Lemeni as Archbishop Tommaso Beckett, 1957-1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 13, Item C13-020)
  - Nicola Rossi Lemeni as Enrico VIII, 1956-1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 13, Item C13-021)
  - Artur Rubinstein, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-022)
  - Max Rudolf, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 13, Item C13-023)
  - Max Rudolf, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-024)
  - Leonie Rysanek as Senta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Buhs, Ilse (Box 13, Item C13-025)
  - Leonie Rysanek as Aida, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 13, Item C13-026)
  - Leonie Rysanek as Elisabeth de Valois, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 13, Item C13-027)
  - Leonie Rysanek, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 13, Item C13-028)
  - Leonie Rysanek as Ariadne, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 13, Item C13-029)
  - Leonie Rysanek as Lady Macbeth, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 13, Item C13-030)
  - Jesus Maria Sanroma, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-031)
  - Jesus Maria Sanroma, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 13, Item C13-032)
  - Jesus Maria Sanroma, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-033)
  - Sir Malcolm Sargent, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Studio Brigg (Box 13, Item C13-034)
  - Sir Malcolm Sargent, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Studio Brigg (Box 13, Item C13-035)
  - Typed thank you note from Malcolm Sargent, 1951 Dec. 5, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-036)
  - Bidú Sayão as Adina, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 13, Item C13-037)
  - Bidú Sayão as Mimi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-038)
  - Bidú Sayão as Violetta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-039)